[
  {
    "question": "Fought in the War of 1812",
    "answers": ["US", "GB"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in World War I",
    "answers": ["US", "GB", "FR", "DE", "RU", "IT", "AU", "CA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in World War II",
    "answers": ["US", "GB", "FR", "DE", "RU", "JP", "IT", "AU", "CA", "CN"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Waterloo",
    "answers": ["GB", "FR", "NL", "DE"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Gettysburg",
    "answers": ["US"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Stalingrad",
    "answers": ["RU", "DE"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Vietnam War",
    "answers": ["US", "VN"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Korean War",
    "answers": ["KR", "CN", "US"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Gulf War",
    "answers": ["US", "UK", "SA", "IQ"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the French Revolution",
    "answers": ["FR", "GB", "DE", "RU", "AT"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Battle of Hastings",
    "answers": ["GB", "FR"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fought in the Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": ["FR", "GB", "DE", "RU", "AT", "ES", "IT", "PL"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Soviet Union",
    "answers": [
      "RU",
      "UA",
      "BY",
      "KZ",
      "LT",
      "LV",
      "EE",
      "MD",
      "KG",
      "TJ",
      "TM",
      "UZ",
      "GE",
      "AM",
      "AZ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the British Empire",
    "answers": [
      "AU",
      "BD",
      "BS",
      "BB",
      "BZ",
      "BW",
      "CA",
      "CY",
      "DM",
      "EG",
      "FJ",
      "GH",
      "GY",
      "IN",
      "JM",
      "KE",
      "KI",
      "MW",
      "MY",
      "MV",
      "MT",
      "MU",
      "NA",
      "NZ",
      "NG",
      "PK",
      "PG",
      "RW",
      "KN",
      "LC",
      "VC",
      "WS",
      "SC",
      "SL",
      "SG",
      "SB",
      "ZA",
      "LK",
      "SD",
      "SZ",
      "TZ",
      "TO",
      "TT",
      "UG",
      "GB",
      "VU",
      "ZM",
      "ZW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Ottoman Empire",
    "answers": [
      "TR",
      "GR",
      "EG",
      "SY",
      "IQ",
      "IL",
      "JO",
      "LB",
      "PS",
      "SA",
      "BH",
      "KW",
      "YE",
      "OM",
      "QA",
      "AE"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the French Empire",
    "answers": [
      "FR",
      "MA",
      "DZ",
      "TN",
      "ML",
      "NE",
      "SN",
      "TD",
      "BJ",
      "BF",
      "GN",
      "MR",
      "CI",
      "CM",
      "MG",
      "CF",
      "GA",
      "CG",
      "DJ",
      "KM"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Spanish Empire",
    "answers": [
      "ES",
      "MX",
      "PE",
      "CO",
      "AR",
      "VE",
      "CL",
      "EC",
      "BO",
      "PY",
      "GT",
      "CU",
      "DO",
      "HN",
      "SV",
      "NI",
      "CR",
      "PA",
      "PH",
      "GQ",
      "GU",
      "MP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Portuguese Empire",
    "answers": ["PT", "BR", "MZ", "AO", "MZ", "CV", "GW", "TL", "ST"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Dutch Empire",
    "answers": ["NL", "ID", "SR", "CW", "SX", "BQ"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Austrian Empire",
    "answers": ["AT", "CZ", "HU", "SI", "HR", "SK", "IT", "PL", "UA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Mongol Empire",
    "answers": [
      "MN",
      "CN",
      "RU",
      "KZ",
      "KG",
      "TJ",
      "UZ",
      "AF",
      "IR",
      "PK",
      "IN",
      "BD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of the Roman Empire",
    "answers": [
      "IT",
      "ES",
      "PT",
      "FR",
      "GB",
      "GR",
      "TN",
      "MA",
      "DZ",
      "LY",
      "EG",
      "IL",
      "TR",
      "AL",
      "ME",
      "RS",
      "SI",
      "HR",
      "BA",
      "MK",
      "BG",
      "RO"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Was formerly a part of Yugoslavia",
    "answers": ["SI", "HR", "BA", "ME", "RS", "MK"]
  }
]
